var quiz = [{"answers": ["Shared", "Privately owned", "Open to a select few", "Government land"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The \u201ccommons\u201d is any area or a resource that is what?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Institutions are formal laws and social norms."}, {"answers": ["May not be aware of the needs of the resources they protect.", "If the government \u201cowns\u201d a resource, it can regulate it.", "Lobbyists can sway government officials to find legal ways to exploit a resource.", "A single government can\u2019t control all resources, like the atmosphere."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following in NOT a problem with government control of common property resources?"}, {"answers": ["An institution", "Social Darwinism", "Tragedy of the Commons", "Prisoner\u2019s dilemma"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "What is the theoretical metaphor for a situation in which a particular action would result in an optimal solution for all, but individual incentive to act selfishly will result in a worse situation for everyone?"}, {"answers": ["Make decisions related to the resource.", "Own property.", "Share the property.", "Negotiate rules or sanctions."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Uneven power relationships make it impossible for some commoners to do all of the following, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Collective action would not include government intervention as a means to protect common property resources."}, {"answers": ["Open access", "Anonymity", "Large populations", "Affluence"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which of the following characteristics is NOT a common resource property problem?"}, {"answers": ["Hard to fence it or lock it off.", "It\u2019s difficult to tell who the violator was.", "An okay behavior for a few is not okay when many do the same.", "It\u2019s hard to save some for others."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Why is open access to a common property resource a problem?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "An institutionalist would most likely suggest privatization as a solution to the \u201cTragedy of the Commons\u201d."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Environmental commons are quite often managed collectively."}, {"answers": ["Many rules ensure sustainability.", "There is no incentive to do the right thing.", "Everyone has access.", "No one own a commons and no one controls it."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a true statement regarding the \u201cTragedy of the Commons\u201d?"}, {"answers": ["Privatization", "Successful lobbying", "Collective Action", "Government Control"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following has NOT been proposed as a way to avoid the \u201cTragedy of the Commons\u201d?"}, {"answers": ["Private owners may own the resource to make a profit.", "None of the choices given is a problem.", "Private owners have many incentives to care for their property.", "Private owners could still exploit resources if the profit motive was large enough."], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which of the following IS a problem with privatization of common property resources?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Failures in protecting a common property resource can result when established rules do not command respect."}, {"answers": ["People who contribute to the Red Cross.", "People who over-harvest to reap all of the benefit.", "People who litter.", "People who listen to public radio, but don\u2019t pay for it."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a \u201cfree-rider\u201d?"}, {"answers": ["Clearly defined boundaries.", "An autonomous system.", "No sanctions to punish violators.", "Costs should match benefits."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following does NOT represent successful commons management?"}, {"answers": ["air", "oceans", "public forest", "climate"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a stationary common property resource?"}, {"answers": ["Ostrom", "Hardin", "Albach", "Malthus"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Who would agree with this statement: \u201cGovernments, international organizations and even some charities unintentionally have caused the destruction of international diversity\u201d?"}, {"answers": ["Privatization", "Collective Action", "Government Control", "Successful lobbying"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The National Park (NPS) system in the U.S. would be an example of which of the following methods to protect common property resources?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Official laws are a type of institution, but social norms are not."}, {"answers": ["The Montreal Protocol", "All of the choices are correct", "Maine lobster fishery management", "Irrigation systems"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of successful collective action to protect common property resources?"}, {"answers": ["When there is a sense of community.", "When we establish strict punishments.", "We allow those affected to assist in monitoring and enforcing.", "When we give those affected a role in setting the rules."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Collective action can work in all of the following situations, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["Prisoner\u2019s dilemma", "Social Darwinism", "Private ownership", "Government regulation"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Hardin theorized that the \u201cTragedy of the Commons\u201d as a particular type of what?"}, {"answers": ["Successful lobbying", "Collective Action", "Privatization", "Government Control"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The statement, \u201cNobody washes a rental car\u201d reflects which of the following ideas for protecting common property resources?"}, {"answers": ["Successful lobbying", "Privatization", "Government Control", "Collective Action"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following did Hardin prefer as a method to avoid the \u201cTragedy of the Commons\u201d?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Hardin argues that in order to prevent the \u201cTragedy of the Commons\u201d, the commons must be enclosed."}, {"answers": ["Collective Action", "Government Control", "Successful lobbying", "Privatization"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Ostrom believed strongly in which of the following methods to protect common property resources?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The concept of Social Darwinism argues that human societies advance primarily through cooperation."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Mobile common property resources are much harder to manage overall."}, {"answers": ["There are currently few incentives to stop polluting.", "Negotiating and enforcing collective rules is an easy solution to implement.", "Pollution such as carbon dioxide does not stay above one country.", "The atmosphere is common property that shared by all countries."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following statements is NOT true regarding the atmosphere as a global commons?"}]

quizCollection['4'] = quiz
